A Guide to the Hunter-Garnett Families Papers, 1806-1889
Special Collections Department, University of Virginia Library
- Correspondence
  - Maria (Hunter) Garnett (1797-1873) to Muscoe Russell Hunter Garnett
    - [to UVa, concern over health, religious support, the confidence between them] 1838 Oct 20 (Box 1)
    - 1838 Oct 22 (Box 1)
      [to UVa, advice on improvement, advises spending time with Walker Gilmer, religious support]
    - 1838 Oct 27 (Box 1)
      [to UVa, concern with his happiness, advice on his education, a visit to Blandfield and description, cousin Muscoe having "a servant at home a most confounded rogue that he wishes to trade" with Muscoe named Da for Serpio, religious support]
    - 1838 Oct 31 (Box 1)
    - 1838 Nov 5 (Box 1)
      [to UVa, Charles [Fenton Mercer Garnett] going to South Carolina to survey the Raleigh and Columbian Road, religious support]
    - 1838 Nov 7 (Box 1)
      [to UVa, planning a visit to Charlottesville, advice on his education, including consulting with [Charles] Bonnycastle (1792-1840), their servant Vira]
    - 1838 Nov 10 (Box 1)
      [to UVa, religious support; with letter from E[lize Lucinda] Garnett]
    - 1838 Dec 1 (Box 1)
      [to UVa, religious support, illness of two servants, Theodore [Stanford Garnett] and his new love Miss [Florentina] Moreno]
    - 1838 Dec 9 (Box 1)
    - 1838 Dec 12 (Box 1)
      [to UVa, a boat trip, religious support, Theodore Garnett and Florentina Moreno, [Charles] Bonnycastle's complement to Muscoe, encouragement re education]
    - 1838 Dec 18 (Box 1)
      [to UVa, concern over his health, encouragement re education]
    - 1839 Jan 23 (Box 1)
      [to UVa, concern over his health, Robert M. T. Hunter and politics, the marriage of Theodore and Florentina no longer being a secret, religious support]
    - 1839 Jan 28 (Box 1)
      [to UVa, the servant Serpio, Robert M. T. Hunter and politics, religious support; with letter from [Grace] Fenton [Garnett Hunter]]
    - 1839 Feb 6 (Box 1)
      [to UVa, inquiries re studies]
    - 1839 Feb 10 (Box 1)
      [to UVa, [Charles] Bonnycastle and Muscoe's studies, religious support]
    - 1839 Feb 13 (Box 1)
      [to UVa, concern over his health and studies]
    - 1839 Feb 15 (Box 1)
      [to UVa, re character-building by self-denial]
    - 1839 Feb 16 (Box 1)
      [to UVa, concern over his health and safety; with letter from S[arah] H. A. Hunter]
    - 1839 Feb 20 (Box 1)
      [to UVa, Robert M. T. Hunter and politics, Margaret [Mercer]'s school and the publishing of her book, Theodore's plans; with letter from S[arah] H. A. Hunter]
    - 1839 Feb 28 (Box 1)
      [to UVa, gardening, need to have Serpio work in the garden as "Old Ben" has been sick, trouble with her servants, Robert M. T. Hunter and politics]
    - 1839 Mar 5 (Box 1)
      [to UVa, [Charles] Bonnycastle, religious support; with letter from E[liza] Garnett, Theodore and Miss Moreno]
    - 1839 Mar 10 (Box 1)
      [to UVa, politics coming between friends]
    - 1839 Mar 13 (Box 1)
      [to UVa, reassuring him about her health, [John] Taliaferro (1768-1852), his studies]
    - 1839 Mar 17 (Box 1)
      [to UVa, [John] Taliaferro, the family of Prospect Hill, [Charles] Bonnycastle and [Gessner] Harrison of the University, thoughts on education and health]
    - 1839 Mar 20 (Box 1)
      [to UVa, an upcoming visit to Charlottesville, her thoughts on education and health]
    - 1839 Mar 23 (Box 1)
      [to UVa, Robert [M. T. Hunter], trying to transfer her negroes]
    - 1839 Mar 27 (Box 1)
      [to UVa, responding to his news of delinquent acts, news of Robert M. T. Hunter's campaign, an upcoming visit to Charlottesville]
    - 1839 Mar 30 (Box 1)
      [to UVa, an upcoming visit, critical of the University and the "Southern Spirit"]
    - 1839 Apr 15 (Box 1)
      [to UVa, safely home after visit, delay of Theodore's marriage]
    - 1839 Apr 16 (Box 1)
      [to UVa, Robert M. T. Hunter's visit, a convention at Bowling Green]
    - 1839 Apr 19 (Box 1)
      [to UVa, [John] Taliaferro]
    - 1839 Apr 23 (Box 1)
      [to UVa, him seeing [Charles] Bonnycastle, his grandfather going to Essex Superior Court, Robert M. T. Hunter being in the middle of a contested election, his uncle Charles Fenton Mercer Garnett's court case, Theodore and Florentina Moreno's plans to marry and their money situation, religious support]
    - 1839 Apr 27 (Box 1)
      [to UVa, Robert M. T. Hunter and his politics and the Whig Party, the death of "a valuable negro boy" by illness, gardening]
    - 1839 May 4 (Box 1)
      [to UVa, politics, Robert M. T. Hunter, Theodore and Florentina]
    - 1839 May 12 (Box 1)
      [to UVa, a trip to Belmead along with those going to the Convention, politics, a pamphlet published by Judge Scott against his uncle [Robert M. T. Hunter]]
    - 1839 May 13 (Box 1)
      [to UVa, politics]
    - 1839 May 14 (Box 1)
    - 1839 May 26 (Box 1)
      [to UVa, concerning his health, typhus fever danger, politics, the election, Robert M. T. Hunter]
    - 1839 May 28 (Box 1)
      [to UVa, personal concerning her anxieties over his well-being, Robert M. T. Hunter and politics]
    - 1839 May (Box 1)
      [to UVa, concerning his disappointment over examinations, offering encouragement]
    - 1839 June 4 (Box 1)
      [to UVa, responding to his inquiry about Serpio]
    - 1839 June 9 (Box 1)
      [to UVa, Robert M. T. Hunter's speech and politics, danger of scarlet fever]
    - 1839 June 18 (Box 1)
      [to UVa, encouragement in studies, advising him to withdraw after mathematics examination, scarlet fever and French measles, Yankees settling in Prince William and Fairfax Counties, John Taliaferro and Robert M. T. Hunter]
    - 1839 June 22 (Box 1)
      [to UVa, examinations, Robert M. T. Hunter visiting him in Charlottesville, an attack of cholera]
    - (Box 1)
    - [1839 June] (Box 1)
      [to UVa, advising him to consult with Robert M. T. Hunter, [Gessner] Harrison, and [Charles] Bonnycastle concerning his studies and graduation; advising him not to sacrifice his health and giving spiritual guidance]
    - (Box 1)
      [additional 4 folders]
  - Maria (Hunter)-Garnett to Muscoe Russell Hunter Garnett
    [additional 9 folders]
  - Mary Barton Picton Garnett (1863-1958) to Maria (Hunter) Garnett (Box 2)
    - 1869 Mar 23 (Box 2)
    - 1870 Jan 20 (Box 2)
      [Pau, France, re riding a donkey and seeing solders drill]
    - 1870 June 25 (Box 2)
      [Geneva, Switzerland, re the new baby and stamp collecting]
    - 1870 July 13 (Box 2)
      [from Mercer, Bagneres-de-Bigorre, France, re a donkey ride "up the Bedat, a mountain with a virgin on the top," and life there; 1870 July 10, from Minnie, with news of the baby, and referring to the beautiful flowers, leaving for Switzerland, and having a war between France and Prussia; 1870 July 30, their arrival in Geneva, Switzerland]
    - 1870 Aug 9 (Box 2)
      [Geneva, Switzerland, re spending the night with Grandma Stevens in Vevey, their studies, traveling to Bern and then on to Interlaken, [New Jersey?]]
    - 1870 Oct 3 (Box 2)
      [Venice, Italy, re their arrival from Milan, a ride on a gondola, a trip to Palace of the Doges and the prison, going to Vevey for a visit, and describing decorations and activities in the streets to please the King]
    - 1870 Oct 18 (Box 2)
      [Munich, Germany, reading Fortunes de Gaspard, news of the baby; 1870 Oct 18, from Mercer, re a visit to a large art gallery and the name of the city, "Muchen" [sic]]
    - 1870 Nov 21 (Box 2)
      [Vevey, Switzerland, news of the baby, reading about how paper is made, activities in Venice and Milan, Italy, and Mrs. McCall]
    - 1870 Dec 3 (Box 2)
      [Vevey, Switzerland, a visit to Mrs. McCall and returning to Italy]
    - 1871 Feb 28 (Box 2)
      [Rome, Italy, seeing Princess Marguerite, going to the Villa Borghese to play, reading Miss Sewell's History of Rome and planning to read History of Greece, lessons on Mississippi, and news of the baby]
    - 1871 May 15 (Box 2)
      [Geneva, Switzerland, re gifts from Miss Wolcott, liking studies; 1871 May 11, from Mercer, re liking school and studies]
    - 1871 May 31 (Box 2)
      [Geneva, Switzerland, reading Geographie Physique, birthday presents, and news of the baby]
    - 1871 Aug 20 (Box 2)
      [from Mercer, Geneva, Switzerland, re a four-week excursion as far as Venice and their activities, learning German; Minnie]
    - 1871 Oct 29 (Box 2)
      [from Mercer, Geneva, Switzerland, re two little German princes and an Egyptian prince, news of little brother Edwin and Etty; 1871 Oct 9, news of Edwin and Etty, and sending a lock of hair]
    - 1872 Feb 16 (Box 2)
      [Nice, France, re taking French lessons]
    - 1872 Mar 23 (Box 2)
      [Menton, France, re visits to Monaco and Monte Carlo, news of Ettie and Edwin, and going to Genoa, Italy]
    - 1873 Jan 27 (Box 2)
      [Paris, France, re mathematics studies, news of Etty and Edwin, attending dance school, and listing the many books received for Christmas]
  - Mary Eleanor Dick (Mercer) Garnett to Muscoe Russell Hunter Garnett
    - n.d. (Box 2)
    - n.d. (Box 2)
      [re a family gathering and Muscoe having the measles]
  - Mary Picton (Stevens) Garnett to Maria (Hunter) Garnett
    - 1864 Jan 27 (Box 2)
      [Richmond, Virginia, inquiring about Mercer who is visiting Grandmother, and re social activities, family news, and Muscoe being ill with a cold]
    - 1864 Aug 4 (Box 2)
      [Manchester, Vermont, re Muscoe's death and her grief and the difficulty in telling the children, and the need for assistance with estate matters]
    - 1864 Nov 2 (Box 2)
      [Hoboken, New Jersey, re children's safe arrival home]
    - 1864 Nov 17 (Box 2)
      [Hoboken, New Jersey, mentioning Mercer, Ettie, and Mary]
    - 1864 Dec 3 (Box 2)
      [Hoboken, New Jersey, re her ill health and of the children]
    - 1864 Dec 9 (Box 2)
      [Hoboken, New Jersey, re health, the death of John Latane (June 20, 1864), aunts "Pink" (Martha T. Hunter) and "Line" (Virginia [ ? ])]
    - 1865 Jan 9 (Box 2)
      [mentions the good health of her son Mercer and Mary's recovery from illness]
    - 1865 Mar 13 (Box 2)
      [Hoboken, New Jersey, personal and family news, and being unable to go south]
    - 1867 Jan 25 (Box 2)
      [Hoboken, New Jersey, written for Mercer, personal, re donkeys and riding in a donkey cart]
    - 1867 Feb 11 (Box 2)
      [Hoboken, New Jersey, written for Mercer, personal; letter from Mary, re finances and estate and debts]
    - 1867 Oct 28 (Box 2)
      [Princeton, New Jersey]
    - 1868 Feb 6 (Box 2)
      [Paris, France, re being seasick onboard ship, description of the vessel and ocean trip, the death of a Frenchman onboard, and the Custom House]
    - 1868 Feb 14 (Box 2)
      [Nice, France, personal and family news, re the lovely view of the sea, and the area being a delightful place for children]
    - 1868 Feb 23 (Box 2)
      [Nice, France, to Mercer, describing little carriages drawn by goats or donkeys, noting that he could learn French, and giving a description of a picnic on a stream; letter to Maria, re financial matters and the purchase of Mt. Pleasant]
    - 1868 Mar 8 (Box 2)
      [Rome, Italy]
    - 1868 Mar 21 (Box 2)
      [Sorrento, Italy, to Mercer, praising his studies and his becoming a big boy, and telling of the killing of a wolf in Pompeii]
    - 1868 Mar 22 (Box 2)
      [Sorrento, Italy, re a visit to Paestum Ruins to see the temples, Salerno, and Amalfi on the bay of Salerno, the danger of the brigands, and the beautiful view from the hotel at the edge of the cliffs]
    - 1868 Apr 5 (Box 2)
      [Rome, Italy, re a visit to Esquiline to see Baths of [ ]--well-preserved ruins, originally house of Marcenas, and relating the history of the area; to the Church of St. Clement, and relating its history; to St. John of [Laterian], describing the beauty of this Roman Catholic Church founded by Constantine; to Villa Borghese to see the collection of statues, including one of Pauline Bonapart]
    - 1868 Apr 19 (Box 2)
      [Rome, Italy, re travel plans in Italy and France, the anticipation in Florence over the arrival of Prince [ ], eldest son of Victor Emanuel, visit to Frascati, celebrations in honor of Pope]
    - 1868 May 3 (Box 2)
      [Florence, Italy, to Mercer, re his Grandmother Stevens staying in Paris, France until July, traveling around France in boats instead of walking, a trip to Albano, Laziale, Italy and a donkey ride to a lake]
    - 1868 May 4 (Box 2)
      [Florence, Italy, re a procession with the royal family in carriages and the American Minister followed by a "firework palace an exact representation of the palace of Potsdam" in honor of the Prince of Prussia, decorated and lit up boats and barges, bands of music--very descriptive letter]
    - 1868 May 19 (Box 2)
      [Milan, Italy, re life there particularly farm life; beggars in Venice, a ride in a gondola, Venice being a charming city; visits to the Rosnian Ampitheatre, to the only monastery in free Italy with closed doors, and to the Cathedral]
    - 1868 May 31 (Box 2)
      [Geneva, Switzerland, re a walk to the Castle of Children and Vevey, and going on a small steamboat up the lake]
    - 1868 June 11 (Box 2)
      [Paris, France, personal and family news, including the newborn]
    - 1868 June 14 (Box 2)
      [Paris, France, to Mercer, personal and family news, including the newborn]
    - 1868 July 13 (Box 2)
      [Paris, Franace, re illness of her father and delayed plans to return home]
    - 1868 Aug 2 (Box 2)
      [Paris, France, re the failing health of her father]
    - 1868 Aug 9 (Box 2)
      [Paris, France, re the death of her father on Friday [August 7] and the baby being sick]
    - 1868 Aug 16 (Box 2)
      [Paris, France, resuming plans to sail home and having to arrange her father's affairs]
    - 1868 Sep 14 (Box 2)
      [Hoboken, New Jersey, re arrival to the United States and her father's funeral]
    - 1868 Oct 15 (Box 2)
      [Hoboken, New Jersey, from Minnie, re having a tea party, a visit to the dentist to have a tooth pulled, and studying French lessions; letter from Mary, personal and family news]
    - 1868 Oct 15 (Box 2)
      [Hoboken, New Jersey, from Mercer, re his activities]
    - 1868 Dec 25 (Box 2)
      [Hoboken, New Jersey, personal, with letters from Minnie and Mercer, re Christmas presents]
    - 1869 Jan 29 (Box 2)
      [Hoboken, New Jersey, enclosing a check and going to seek advice about the western lands]
    - 1869 Dec 19 (Box 2)
      [Pau, France, personal news of herself and the children]
    - 1870 Dec 20 (Box 2)
      [Rome, Italy, re business matters, informing her that the business affairs should be known to her husband and that she will consult Mr. Lewis on all matters; the atmosphere in Rome]
    - 1872 Apr 8 (Box 2)
      [Florence, Italy, concerning their strained relationship and her feeling insulted by Maria's actions, and family news]
    - n.y. Feb 23 (Box 2)
      [Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, personal and family news]
    - Thursday morning (Box 2)
      [ante-1864, re Muscoe being unable to attend court, and personal and family news]
    - Sunday afternoon (Box 2)
      [ante-1864, re Muscoe visiting Font Hill alone because she is unable to get away until the following week]
    - Wednesday evening (Box 2)
      [Roxbury, re her travel plans to Font Hill, circumstances during the Civil War, and personal and family news]
    - Sunday (Box 2)
      [asking her to pay the taxes on their mountain lands]
    - n.d. (Box 2)
      [note re business matters concerning the Nicholas and Coal property]
  - Theodore Stanford (1812-1885) and Florentina I. (Moreno) Garnett to Muscoe Russell Hunter Garnett and Maria Hunter Garnett
    - 1832 Jan 24 (Box 2)
      [Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, to Muscoe, prompting him to write more frequently in order "to acquire a facility in expressing your thoughts on paper...," encouraging his progres in school; brief description of Philadelphia in response to an inquiry, including the Theatre which "is now miserably perverted from the first object of the stage," the Museum and its natural curiosities, the Athaneum, the Academy of Fine Arts, the Mint, and the Deaf and Dumb Asylum and its accomplishments]
    - 1833 May 14 (Box 2)
      [New Castle, Virginia, to Muscoe, encouraging his studies]
    - 1834 Feb 17 (Box 2)
      [Pemberly, Mason County, Virginia, to Muscoe, commenting on his improvement in writing, encouraging regular exercise, and describing his pets, a puppy and a doe]
    - 1837 Sep 9 (Box 2)
      [Pensacola, Florida, to Muscoe, advising him to go to the University of Virginia right away, warning him against the "bad" and telling him to choose gentlemen for his associates]
    - 1845 Jan 21 (Box 2)
      [Richmond, Virginia, to Muscoe, re an account held against his father and seeking assistance with the matter]
    - 1845 Mar 11 (Box 2)
      [Richmond, Virginia, to Muscoe, re plans to "negotiate a treatly of commerce between Rapp[ahannock] and James Rivers," and the Southern Democracy and politics]
    - 1847 Jan 22 (Box 2)
      [Loretto, Virginia, Florentina to Maria, requesting to see the doctor concerning her teeth]
    - 1848 July 28 (Box 2)
      [Columbia, South Carolina, to Muscoe, concerning Union supporters, the theory of Republican government, Taylor and Burr and their politics, and his own opinions]
    - 1850 Nov 28 (Box 2)
      [Macon, Georgia, to Maria, concerning the interest in North Carolina over Muscoe's election, and family news]
  - Gessner Harrison (1807-1862) to Muscoe Russell Hunter Garnett
    - 1856 Apr 14 (Box 2)
      [University of Virginia, while Chair of Ancient Languages, concenring his appreciation of Muscoe's flattering letter, saying that his ambition has merely been "to discharge faithfully my duties" at the University, hoping that his service has been useful to their alma mater; re financial burden and attempting to start a boarding school for boys, meager salary at the University not being enough to support his family]
  - Grace Fenton (Garnett) Hunter to Maria (Hunter) Garnett and Muscoe Russell Hunter Garnett
    - 1838 Aug 4 (Box 2)
      [Candlelight, Red Sue Springs, Virginia, to Maria, re their improving health at the springs, and news of others there]
    - 1838 Oct 8 (Box 2)
      [to Muscoe, re plans to make fortune by cultivating multicaulis, personal and family news, mention of the University of Virginia; with letter from Eliza, re their faith in him doing well at the University]
    - 1839 May 20 (Box 2)
      [Norfolk, Virginia, to Muscoe, University of Virginia, personal and family news and church attendance]
    - n.y. Dec 4 (Box 2)
      [Fonthill, Virginia, to Muscoe]
    - n.d. Friday 19th (Box 2)
      [Elmwood, to Muscoe, University of Virginia, family news, Belmont School being full and taking on additional scholars]
    - n.d. Saturday morning (Box 2)
      [to Maria, personal and family news]
  - James Hunter (1774-1826) to Maria (Hunter) Garnett
    - 1813 July 18 (Box 2)
      [Charlottesville, Virginia, re beauty of Peter's Mountain; being within two miles of Monticello and having the "opportunity of an easy introduction to its sage" but not availing himself of it, and some comments on Thomas Jefferson; and having received "information of the progress of the British up the Potomac"]
    - 1819 Jan 23 (Box 2)
      [Richmond, Virginia, concerning her taking over the gardening duties, Mrs. French's concerts, and visits to the theatre]
  - Jane Swann Hunter (1804-1880) to Muscoe Russell Hunter Garnett
    - 1839 Apr 23 (Box 2)
      [to UVa, re education during that time period, and continued efforts to establish a comprehensive public school system]
    - [1841] Oct 30 (Box 2)
      [to UVa, re the Whig meeting, political affairs at the time of the Fiscal Bank vetoes, and Robert Mercer Taliaferro Hunter]
    - 1841 Oct 3 (Box 2)
      [to UVa, personal, mentions R. M. T. Hunter]
    - 1842 Feb 7 (Box 2)
      [to UVa, personal, discussing the ideas of universality and existence; with letter from Maria Hunter Garnett]
    - n.y. Dec 5 (Box 2)
      [personal, mentions Robert [M. T. Hunter]]
    - n.d. (Box 2)
      [advice and support (prior to his going away to college)]
    - n.d. (Box 2)
      [to Mercer, personal, re children playing Indians, jaybirds and the cats]
  - Maria (Garnett) Hunter (1777-1811) to family
    - 1797 Mar 8 (Box 2)
      [to Charles Fenton Mercer Garnett, re leaving Norfolk because of smallpox; the strong friendship between them; being envious of his going to college, saying "a life which would have been so much to my taste if my sex had not excluded me from it"]
    - 1810 Jan (Box 2)
      [to Maria Hunter, to her daughters who are away with friends in order to "acquire knowledge...which will be a gratification to the end of your life"]
    - 1810 (Box 2)
      [to Maria Hunter, her daughter, personal]
    - n.d. (Box 2)
      [personal and family news, smallpox in the family]
    - n.d. (Box 2)
      [to Fenton, personal and family news, Albert [R. Garnett]'s illness and Yelverton's death]
    - n.d. (Box 2)
      [to Mrs. Mary E[leanor] Garnett, family news; with letter from G[race]; F[enton Hunter] Garnett, personal]
    - n.d. (Box 2)
      [to Maria Hunter, her daughter, giving advice and support concerning her character and conduct in relationship to the sciences and religion, and not wishing to discourage the "pursuit of knowledge not immediately connected with religion"]
    - n.d. (Box 2)
      [to Mary Eleanor Mercer, personal]
  - Martha Fenton Hunter (1800-1866) to Muscoe Russell Hunter Garnett and David W. Pitts
    - n.y. [1830s?] Jan 26 (Box 2)
      [personal, discussing abolitionist movement and requesting that he propose an amendment]
    - n.y. [1856?] Feb 15 (Box 2)
      [re politics, the fear of having a "Black Republican President," and the disregard for the South in Congress]
    - n.y. Feb 18 (Box 2)
      [to UVa, mentioning the genius of Bacon Shakespeare Scott; Mr. [ ] Sylvester's kindness to Muscoe but warning him that "his metaphysical speculations may be closely connected with German infidelity"; news of family and friends; Albert Micon setting out for Alabama; translating Discourse on Universal History[by Jacques Benigne Bossuet]; and politics--the Committee of Foreign Affairs members withdrawing and Holmes refusing to serve]
    - n.y. May 6 (Box 2)
      [to UVa, news of the family, Robert [M. T. Hunter] and politics and "States Rights men"]
    - n.y. Dec 7 (Box 2)
      [to Washington, D. C., personal, mentioning Robert [M. T. Hunter]
    - n.d. (Box 2)
      ["reply to a proposal of marriage about 100 years ago" to Mr. David W. Pitts]
  - Martha Taliaferro Hunter (1778-1840) to family
    - 1837 Aug 8 (Box 2)
      [to Muscoe Russell Hunter Garnett, family and local news; with note from Sarah H. A. Hunter]
    - 1839 May 7 (Box 2)
      [to Muscoe Russell Hunter Garnett, UVa, family and local news, R. M. T. Hunter, local elections, and [John] Mercer [Garnett]]
    - n.y. Nov 5 (Box 2)
      [to MRHG, UVa, family and local news]
    - n.d. (Box 2)
    - n.d. (Box 2)
      [to Grace Fenton Hunter, personal]
    - n.d. (Box 2)
      [to Maria Hunter Garnett, family news]
    - n.d. (Box 2)
    - n.d. (Box 2)
      [3 ANs, personal]
    - n.d. (Box 2)
      [to Edgar M. Hunter, personal]
  - Martha Taliaferro "Pink" Hunter to Mary Picton (Stevens) Garnett
    - 1858 May 11 (Box 2)
    - 1858 (Box 2)
  - Muscoe Garnett Hunter to Maria (Hunter) Garnett
    - 1816 Oct 30 (Box 2)
  - Robert Mercer Taliaferro Hunter to Roger Atkinson Pryor, and related
    - 1857 Feb 26 (Box 2)
    - 1857 Mar 25 (Box 2)
  - Robert Mercer Taliaferro Hunter to L. Q. Washington
    - 1865 July 7 (Box 2)
    - 1865 Aug 1 (Box 2)